fsiblog.com 2019-12-31

# Privacy Policy - FSI Blog

**Welcome, and thank you for your interest in freesexyindians.com** **(“** **site”** **, “we” or “us”), and all related websites, downloadable software, mobile applications (including tablet applications), and other services provided by us and on which a link to this Privacy Policy is displayed, and all other communications with individuals through email.**

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) describes the information that we gather on or through the Service, how we use and disclose such information, and the steps we take to protect such information. By visiting the Site, or by purchasing or using the Service, you accept the privacy practices described in this Policy.

## Definition

  * **User:** The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.
  * **Personal Data:** means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.
  * **Public Area:** means the area of the Site that can be accessed both by Users and Visitors, without needing to log in.
  * **Restricted Area:** means the area of the Site that can be accessed only by Users, and where access requires logging in.
  * **Visitor:** means an individual other than a User, who uses the public area, but has no access to the restricted areas of the Site or Service.
  * **Cookies:** Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

## 1\. What information do we collect?

### 1.1 Personal Data

While using our site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally, identifiable information may include, but is not limited to: Email address, Name, “About you” information, your submitted content, Cookies and Usage Data.

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send. 

If you want to create an account on our sites you have to provide your email and pick a username. If you don’t provide this data you can’t create the account. 

### 1.2 Usage Data

We may also collect information on how the Service is accessed and used (“Usage Data”). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

### 1.3 Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use: **session cookies** (we use these cookies to operate our Service) and **preference cookies** (we use these cookies to remember your preferences and various settings).

## 2\. How We Use the Information We Collect

We use the information that we collect in a variety of ways in providing the Service and operating our business, including the following:

### 2.1 Operations

We use the information to operate, maintain, enhance and provide all features of the Service, to provide the services and information that you request, to respond to comments and questions and to provide support to users of the Service.

### 2.2 Improvements

We use the information to understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of our Visitors and Users, to improve the Service, and to develop new products, services, feature, and functionality. 

### 2.3 Communication

We may use your email address to contact you for administrative purposes such as customer service, to address intellectual property infringement, the right of privacy violations or defamation issues related to the Personal Data. You have the ability to opt-out of receiving any promotional communications.

### 2.4 Cookies and Tracking Technologies

We use automatically collected information and other information collected on the Service through cookies and similar technologies to (i) personalize our Service, such as remembering a User’s or Visitor’s information so that the User or Visitor will not have to re-enter it during a visit or on subsequent visits; (ii) provide customized advertisements, content, and information; (iii) monitor and analyze the effectiveness of Service and third-party marketing activities; (iv) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (v) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities on the Service. You can obtain more information about cookies by visiting [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

### 2.5 Analytics

We use Google Analytics to measure and evaluate access to and traffic on the Site and create user navigation reports for our Site administrators. Google operates independently from us and has its own privacy policy, which we strongly suggest you review. Google may use the information collected through Google Analytics to evaluate Users’ and Visitors’ activity on our Site. For more information, see [Google Analytics Privacy and Data Sharing](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245).

We take measures to protect the technical information collected by our use of Google Analytics. The data collected will only be used on a need to know basis to resolve technical issues, administer the Site and identify visitor preferences; but in this case, the data will be in non-identifiable form. We do not use any of this information to identify Visitors or Users.

## 3\. To Whom We Disclose Information

Except as described in this Policy, we will not intentionally disclose the Personal Data that we collect or store on the Service to third parties without the consent of the applicable Visitor or User. We may disclose information to third parties if you consent to us doing so, as well as in the following circumstances:

### 3.1 Unrestricted Information

Any information that you voluntarily choose to include in a Public Area of the Service, such as a public profile page, will be available to any Visitor or User who has access to that content.

### 3.2 Service Providers

We work with third-party service providers who provide the website, application development, hosting, maintenance, and other services for us. These third parties may have access to, or process Personal Data as part of providing those services for us. We limit the information provided to these service providers to that which is reasonably necessary for them to perform their functions, and our contracts with them require them to maintain the confidentiality of such information.

### 3.3 Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may make certain automatically-collected, aggregated, or otherwise non-personally-identifiable information available to third parties for various purposes, including (i) compliance with various reporting obligations; (ii) for business or marketing purposes; or (iii) to assist such parties in understanding our Users’ and Visitors’ interests, habits, and usage patterns for certain programs, content, services, and/or functionality available through the Service.

## 4\. Your Rights

We aim to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

Whenever made possible, you can update your Personal Data directly within your account settings section. If you are unable to change your Personal Data, please contact us to make the required changes.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

  * To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you
  * To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate
  * To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you

You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to us. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

## 5\. Third-Party Services

The Service may contain features or links to websites and services provided by third parties. Any information you provide on third-party sites or services is provided directly to the operators of such services and is subject to those operators’ policies, if any, governing privacy and security, even if accessed through the Service. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of third-party sites or services to which links or access are provided through the site. We encourage you to learn about third parties’ privacy and security policies before providing them with information.

## 6\. Data Retention

We only retain the Personal Data collected from a User for as long as the User’s account is active or otherwise for a limited period of time as long as we need it to fulfil the purposes for which we have initially collected it unless otherwise required by law. 

## 7\. Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## 8\. Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked websites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our website and welcome any feedback about these websites.

## 9\. Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

The site does not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties any personally identifiable information.

This does not include trusted third parties or subcontractors who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you. Such trusted parties may have access to personally identifiable information on a need-to-know basis and will be contractually obliged to keep your information confidential.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety. Furthermore, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## 10\. Data controller

We are Data controller of your data as defined in terms of the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation (EU) 2016/679).

## 11\. Changes and Updates to this Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

## 12\. How to contact us

Please contact us with any questions or comments about this Policy, your Personal Data, our use and disclosure practices, or your consent choices by email at[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Last update: 11.5. 2018
